Guide to the John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955,
Comstock, John Henry and Anna Botsford papers,
- Correspondence
  - John Henry Comstock professional correspondence
    - Wheeler, Benjamin Ide, 1900-03-26 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Wheelock, Charles Brackett, 1890-08-18 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Wheelock, Charles Brackett, 1891-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Whipple, J.A., 1894-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Marine Biological Laboratory
    - Whitcomb, H.T., 1885-09-14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Whitcomb, H.T., 1887-08-15 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Whitcomb, H.T., 1889-08-16 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Whitcomb, H.T., 1892-06-16 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - White and Burdick, 1886-01 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Drugs and Chemicals
    - White and Burdick, 1887-01-13 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - White and Burdick, 1889-06-10 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - White and Burdick, 1889-07-23 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - White and Burdick, 1890-04-15 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - White and Burdick, 1891-08-14 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - White and Burdick, 1893-01-01 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - White and Burdick, 1894-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - White, Andrew Curtis, 1888-08-29 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Assistant Librarian Cornell
    - White, Andrew Curtis, 1892-05-24 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - White, Andrew Dickson, 1885-03-02 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - White, Andrew Dickson, 1896-10-28 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - White, Andrew Dickson, 1898-08-22 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - White, Frederick Davies, 1886-08-05 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - White, James T. and Company, 1890-09-26 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      publishers
    - White, James T. and Company, 1890-11-10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - White, James T. and Company, 1891-07-30 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - White, James T. and Company, 1891-08-27 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Whitehead, Charles, 1889-01-22 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Whitehead, Charles, 1889-04-23 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Whitehead, Charles, 1892-05-31 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Whitelaw, William, 1889-07-17 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1885-09-30 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Manufacturers of glassware
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1887-03-10 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1887-04-10 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1887-09-16 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1887-09-22 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1887-10-04 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1887-10-10 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-05-18 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-06-06 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-06-11 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-06-14 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-06-25 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-06-26 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-06-28 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-07-07 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-10 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1888-11-23 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-05-12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-05-17 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-05-21 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-05-22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-05-28 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-06-22 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-06-28 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-07-07 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-07-18 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-08-09 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-08-13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1889-10 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1890-05-15 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1890-06-06 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1890-06-23 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1890-06-25 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1890-08-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1891-04-29 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1891-06-30 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1891-07-01 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1891-07-27 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, 1892-05-19 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Whithall, Tatum and Company, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Whitlock, A., 1890-05-01 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Whiton, J.L., 1886-02-16 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1891-08-22 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1892-04-15 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1892-12-05 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1893-10-14 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1893-10-28 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1893-11-18 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1894-08-13 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1894-08-24 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, 1896-04-02 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Wickham, Henry Frederick, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Wickson, Edward James, 1887-03-24 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Professor, Horticulturist
    - Wickson, Edward James, 1887-04-08 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Wickson, Edward James, 1889-06 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Wickson, Edward James, 1892-11-05 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Wickson, G.G. and Company, 1893-03-11 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Remington Typewriter Rentals
    - Widow, The, 1898-01-06 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Wiese Brothers, 1901-01-04 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Wight, R. Allan, 1889-10-07 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Wilcox, Earley Vernon, 1891-09-04 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1886-01-15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Professor of Physiology, Zoology
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1886-01-25 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1886-01-30 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1887-08-08 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1887-11-16 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1889-08-16 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1889-08-29 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1890-03-31 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1890-10-27 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1891-07-27 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1891-08-04 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1891-08-10 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wilder, Burt Green, 1892-08-08 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Wilkinson, G.E., 1892-06 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Wilkinson, G.E., 1892-06-04 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Willard, S.D., 1892-09-09 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      of Hammond and Willard; Nurseries
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1889-05-03 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1890-05-27 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1890-09-21 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1891-09-11 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1891-09-25 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1891-10-05 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1891-10-07 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1891-11-27 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, 1891-12-05 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Willcox, Mary Alice, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Willet, J.E., 1889-01-19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Mercer University
    - Williams, Anna Phillips, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Sec.; Marine Biological Labs
    - Williams, C.E., 1890-02-10 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Manager; Sutter County Fruit Company, CA
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1885-11-25 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Treasurer of Cornell
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1886-04-20 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1887-02-19 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1887-07-22 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1887-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1889-04-17 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1889-09-30 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-01-08 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-03-31 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-06-05 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-08-04 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-10-03 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-10-27 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-10-29 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1890-10-30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1891-04-23 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1891-04-25 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1891-05-27 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1891-07-25 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1891-11-11 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1892-04-14 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1892-06-11 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1892-10-29 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1893-04-11 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1893-12-04 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Emmons L., 1894-10-18 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Williams, George Russell, 1885-11-21 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Trustee, Cornell
    - Williams, Harry S., 1886-02-23 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Mrs. Josiah B., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Tom A., 1889-11-07 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Williams, Tom A., 1890-01-29 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Williams, Tom A., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1890-01-07 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Paleontologist
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1890-02-20 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1890-02-23 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1891-02-22 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1891-02-23 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1891-09-21 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1892-05-22 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1893-02-14 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1893-03-19 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1893-06-19 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1893-07-21 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1894-05-20 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1894-05-28 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1894-06-10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1894-09-03 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Williston, Samuel Wendell, 1896-09-07 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Willits, Edwin, 1889-07-29 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Assistant Secretary of Agriculture; Department of Agriculture, Washington DC
    - Willits, Edwin, 1889-09-02 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Wilsey, O.J., 1888-04-16 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Wilsey, O.J., 1888-07-13 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Wilson, F.G., 1890-11-10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Jewelers
    - Wilson, F.G., 1891-05-27 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, James Meredith, 1885-04-24 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, James Meredith, 1888-08-05 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, James Meredith, 1889-05-13 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, P.B., 1891-06-01 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, R.K., 1891-07-09 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, William Powell, 1890-10-15 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1888-10-25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Cornell Agricultural Station
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1889-05-20 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1889-06-05 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1889-10-17 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1889-10-29 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1890-01-20 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1890-04-07 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1891-06-29 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1891-11-05 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1892-05-02 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Wing, Henry Hiram, 1894-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Winser, John H., 1889-04-11 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Winslow, John, 1887-01-01 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Doctor
    - Winslow, John, 1887-04-01 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Winslow, John, 1887-12-31 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Winslow, John, 1888-07-11 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Winslow, John, 1888-12-17 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Winslow, John, 1889-11-01 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Winslow, John, 1890-12-29 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Winslow, John, 1891-11-10 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Winslow, John, 1893-12-15 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Wisner, Henry C., 1890-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Withington, Alfreda Bosworth, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Wood, D.R., 1889-12-31 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Wood, D.R., 1891-08-24 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wood, D.R., 1891-09-04 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Woodason, Thomas, 1889-11-20 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Woodason Bellows Works
    - Woodbury, C.D., 1890-03-03 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Woodruff, Edwin Hamlin, 1891-02-22 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Woodruff, Edwin Hamlin, 1891-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Woodruff, Edwin Hamlin, 1893-10-31 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Woodruff, Edwin Hamlin, 1894-09-17 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Woodward, J.S., 1887-09-28 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Sec.; NY State Agricultural Society
    - Woodward, J.S., 1887-10-06 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Woodward, J.S., 1887-11-28 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Woodward, J.S., 1888-05-26 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Woodward, J.S., 1889-04-30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Woodward, J.S., 1889-09-27 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Woodward, J.S., 1890-03-13 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Woodworth, Charles William, 1900-03-14 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Professor, Entomologist
    - Woodworth, Charles William, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Woodworth, Howard Oakley, 1896-04-29 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Woodworth, Howard Oakley, 1896-11-24 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Woodworth, William McMichael, 1899-02-15 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Woodworth, William McMichael, 1899-02-26 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Worthington, Thomas Jr., 1890-09-03 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Worthington, Thomas Jr., 1891-12-04 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Worthington, Thomas Jr., 1892-02-06 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Worthington, Thomas Jr., 1892-07-13 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Wright, Albert Allen, 1893-04-20 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Professor, Geologist, Zoologist
    - Wright, Albert Allen, 1893-05-06 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Wright, Albert Allen, 1894-04-20 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Wright, E.M., 1898-11-04 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Wright, Peter and Sons, 1888-11-13 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      General Agents
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1886-04-02 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      remington typewriter
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1886-04-10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1886-04-29 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1890-10-30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1890-11-01 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1890-11-08 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1890-11-12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1890-11-29 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1890-12-12 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1891-01-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Wyckoff, W.O., 1892-04-05 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Wykoff, Peter, 1890-05-07 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company, 1886-05-12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Key manufacturers
    - Yanger, J. Frank, 1887-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Yeomans, T.G. and Sons, 1889-05-11 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Nurserymen and Fruit-Growers
    - Yeomans, T.G. and Sons, 1896-10-28 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Yeomans, T.G. and Sons, 1896-11-04 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - York, Miss E.E., 1892-02-29 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Youmans, Charles M., 1891-04-14 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      of Youmans Brothers and Hodgins, Lumber Manufacturers
    - Youmans, Charles M., 1892-09-13 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Young, D.B., 1890-02-08 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Young, D.B., 1890-02-24 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Zacktein Company, 1888-10-08 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Zavitz, C.A., 1889-12-27 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Ontario Agricultural College
    - Zavitz, C.A., 1890-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Zavitz, C.A., 1890-11-05 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Zavitz, C.A., 1890-11-08 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Zavitz, C.A., 1890-11-11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Zavitz, C.A., 1890-11-13 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Zimmerman, C.D., 1889-03-05 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Zimmerman, C.D., 1889-11-20 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- John Henry Comstock certificates and newspaper clippings, 1878-1931
  - Certificates and awards, 1878-1922
    - Marriage certificate, 1878-10-07 (Box 6)
    - Persident's First Prize, Cornell, 1872-06-27 (Box 6)
    - B.S. degree, Cornell, 1874-07-02 (Box 6)
    - Fellowship in American Association Advancement of Science, 1882-08 (Box 6)
    - Membership in Societe Entomologique de France, 1888-12-12 (Box 6)
    - Election to American Entomological Society, 1898-04-28 (Box 6)
    - California Academy of Sciences of San Francisco, honorary member, 1903-01-05 (Box 6)
    - Elected member, American Association Advancement of Science, 1905-06-25 (Box 6)
    - Elected fellow, American Association Advancement of Science, 1906-01-01 (Box 6)
    - Elected fellow to American Entomological Society, 1906-12-28 (Box 6)
    - Birthday greeting from Jugatae Club, 1927 (Box 6)
    - Named member of permanent Committee of International Congress of Entomology, 1910-10-01 (Box 6)
    - Honorary Fellow, Entomological Society of London, 1911-11-09 (Box 6)
    - Honorary Fellow, Entomological Society of America, 1914-12-30 (Box 6)
    - Correspondent, Academy of Natural Sciences, Philadelphia, 1918-03-19 (Box 6)
    - Sociedade Entomologica de Brasil, Honorary membership, 1922-04-20 (Box 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1885-1931
    - "Summer School of Entomology", Cornell Daily Sun, 1885-09-25 (Box 6)
    - "Comstock Library Duly Presented as Memorial", Ithaca Journal, 1914-06-15 (Box 6)
    - "Entomologists Save Many Crops from Bug Pests" Honolulu Star Bulletin, 1925-01-31 (Box 6)
    - Comstocks on 50th Anniversary (Box 6)
    - "Mrs Comstock Dies; Famous Many Years as Teacher, Artist", Ithaca Journal-News, 1930-08-23 (Box 6)
    - "Comstock Rites 3pm Sunday Sage Chapel", Ithaca Hournal-News, 1931-03-21 (Box 6)
    - "Professor J.H. Comstock, Entomologist, Dies" New York Times, 1931-03-22 (Box 6)
    - Article on Professor Hiram Corson from the Troy Daily Times, 1899-04-22 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Anna Botsford Comstock materials, 1873-1968
  - Certificates, 1873-1901 (Box 7)
  - Diaries, 1870-1875 (Box 7)
    Skips 1872-1873
  - Stamp case, fragments, and autographs, Undated (Box 7)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 7)
  - Poem: "The Old Farm at Cornell.", Undated (Box 7)
  - The Theta Brook Song by Anna Botsford Comstock, Undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Two Incarnations in Stripes (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Misc items (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Jottings - Spiders (Box 26)
- Lecture and field notes
  - Field notes, 1891-1901 (Box 7)
  - Syllabus of Nature Study lectures, Undated (Box 7)
  - Outlines of Lectures on Zoology, Undated (Box 7)
- Anna Botsford Comstock autobiography, Undated
  Published as The Comstocks of Cornell: John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock, edited by Glenn W. Herrick Ruby Green Smith, 1953
  - Genealogical notes, Undated (Box 8)
  - Chapters 1-13 and 15-20, Undated (Box 8)
- Printed material, 1888-1968
  - An Introduction to Entomology, John Henry Comstock, 1895 (Box 9)
  - A Manual for the Study of Insects, John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock, 1903 (Box 9)
  - Ways of the Six Footed, Anna Botsford Comstock, 1913 (Box 9)
  - Retirement of Professor John Henry Comstock, S.H. Gage, 1914 (Box 9)
  - Reports om Scale Insects, John Henry Comstock, 1916 (Box 9)
  - Trees at Leisure, Anna Botsford Comstock, 1916 (Box 9)
  - The Common Butterflies: An Outline for Butterfly Study, Anna Botsford Comstock, 1917 (Box 9)
  - "Professor John Henry Comstock" Annals of the Entomological Society of America, 1931 (Box 9)
  - Resolution of the Trustees and Faculty of Cornell University on the Death of John Henry Comstock Emeritus Professor of Entomology, 1930-12 (Box 9)
  - Resolution of the Trustees and Faculty of Cornell University on the Death of Anna Botsford Comstock, Professor of Nature Study Emeritus, 1931-09 (Box 9)
  - Partners in Science, Alma Smith Payne, 1968 (Box 9)
- Botsford and Comstock family photographs, Undated
  - Botsford and Comstock family photographs, 1877-1929; 8 x 11 cm, 25.5 x 31 cm; Some photographs mounted on board, including cabinet cards and cartes-de-visite. (Box 10, Folder 1-45)
    Photographs include portraits of Anna Botsford Comstock and John Henry Comstock, their parents and relatives, as well as photographs of their home and gardens. Also included is a photograph of the first entomology building on Cornell campus (1888), and several group portraits of Cornell students and faculty.
    Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1854-1930
    Comstock, John Henry, 1849-1931
    Gelatin silver print
    albumen prints
    tintypes (prints)
    negatives (photographs)
    platinum prints
  - Oversized photograph of Anna Botsford's father, Undated (Box 11)
  - Autochromes of the Comstocks, 1907-1930; 6 autochromes (Box 27)
    Gardens
    Autochromes
    Access only by permission of curator. Fragile, require careful handling.
    - Anna Botsford Comstock in the garden, 12.7 x 10.2 cm (Box 27)
    - Anna Botsford Comstock on a bench in her garden, 10.2 x 12.7 cm (Box 27)
    - John Henry Comstock and Anna Botsford Comstock on a bench in their garden, 10.2 x 12.7 cm (Box 27)
    - The Comstocks at their gate, 124 Roberts Place, 12.7 x 10.2 cm (Box 27)
    - Anna Botsford Comstock and John Henry Comstock on a bench in their garden, 12.7 x 10.2 cm (Box 27)
    - Anna Botsford Comstock and John Henry Comstock on a bench in their garden, 10.2 x 12.7 cm (Box 27)
- Wood engravings, sketches, drawings, and photographs by Anna Botsford Comstock, 1891-1930
  - Engravings, 1891-1896
    - Wood engravings of plants, a tiger, and Cornell University., Undated (Box 11)
    - Spider web and flowers "to Martha Van Rennselaer", Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Dandelions "to Nannie", Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Daisies " to Mag", Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Moth "to Marguerite Hempstead", Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Moth "Engraved for Nature", 1891 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Three butterflies "Engraved for Nature", 1891 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Moth "to J.L. Lloyd", 1891 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - McGraw (Uris Library) and Sage Chapel, Cornell University, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Wooded path "to Mr. and Mrs. Duggan", Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Fall Creek lagoon "to Mrs. H.S. Williams", Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Coy Glen "to Professor Henry S. Williams", Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Wooded path "to Nannie", 1896 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Wooded path " to Glenn Herrick", Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - McGraw Tower (Uris Library), Cornell University "to George R. Burr", Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Lilies "to Glenn and Nannie", Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Tiger and butterfly "to Glenn Herrick", 1895 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Five moths and butterflies, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      On deposit from Comstock Memorial Library of Entomology
    - Lilies with spider web, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Matted engravings, Undated (Box 23)
    - Matted engravings, Undated (Box 24)
    - Engravings, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Framed engraving of "A Woodland Path" signed by Anna Comstock to Mrs. St. John (Box 28)
  - Tools and materials for engraving
    - Materials pertaining to wood engraving, Undated (Box 7)
    - Wooden printing block for "moths on a moonlit night", Undated (Box 15)
      Engraved by Anna Botsford Comstock
    - Engraving tools, Undated; MU-2070 (Box 21)
    - Printing and engraving techniques, Undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Bronze medal from the Pan-American Exposition, Buffalo, New York, 1901 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Watercolors, Undated